let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What is PHP?",
        answer: "All of the mentioned",
        options: [
            "PHP is an open-source programming language",
            "PHP is used to develop dynamic and interactive websites",
            "PHP is a server-side scripting language",
            "All of the mentioned"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "What does PHP stand for?",
        answer: "PHP stands for Hypertext Preprocessor",
        options: [
            "PHP stands for Preprocessor Home Page",
            "PHP stands for Pretext Hypertext Processor",
            "PHP stands for Hypertext Preprocessor",
            "PHP stands for Personal Hyper Processor"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Which of the following is used for concatenation in PHP?",
        answer: ". (dot)",
        options: [
            "+ (plus)",
            "* (Asterisk)",
            ". (dot)",
            "append()"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Which of the following is the correct way to add a comment in PHP code?",
        answer: "All of the mentioned",
        options: [
            "#",
            "//",
            "/* */",
            "All of the mentioned"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Which is the right way of declaring a variable in PHP?",
        answer: "$_hello",
        options: [
            "$3hello",
            "$_hello",
            "$this",
            "$5_Hello"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "A function in PHP which starts with __ (double underscore) is known as __________",
        answer: "Magic Function",
        options: [
            "Default Function",
            "User Defined Function",
            "Inbuilt Function",
            "Magic Function"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "PHP recognizes constructors by the name _________",
        answer: "function __construct()",
        options: [
            "function __construct()",
            "function _construct()",
            "classname()",
            "_construct()"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "What does PDO stand for?",
        answer: "PHP Data Object",
        options: [
            "PHP Database Orientation",
            "PHP Data Orientation",
            "PHP Data Object",
            "PHP Database Object"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Which version of PHP introduced the advanced concepts of OOP?",
        answer: "PHP 5",
        options: [
            "PHP 6",
            "PHP 4",
            "PHP 5",
            "PHP 5.3"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "If $a = 12 what will be returned when ($a == 12) ? 5 : 1 is executed?",
        answer: "5",
        options: [
            "1",
            "5",
            "12",
            "Error"
        ]
    }
]